Once again, today, the maidens who gather
in the gardens of the wisdom king
cross the Tama River with smiles as
pure as those of the Shinsengumi troopers.
Their bodies and hearts, never once
sullied, are clad in pure white clothes.
The pleats of their skirts
without a single wrinkle,
their blue sailor scarves
not even flapping in the wind.
They walk slowly, as
manners dictate they should.
South Hino High School:
this is the garden of maidens.
(a coed school)
Good morning to you, lovely viewers!
Shika! shika, shika, shika! Shika!
GIRL MEETS DEER
It's still so coooold!
And it rained yesterday, too!
It's slippery, so you have to be careful.
Are you okay?
Erm… Thank you very much!
You're welcome.
Torako Koshi, a second-year student
at South Hino High School,
the president of the student council,
as well as the class rep for Class 2B.
And also, she's attractive,
great at school, and prolific in sports.
And not only at school, but also in neighborhood,
she's revered as a perfect girl.
She's wonderful!
Just as I planned!
But Torako Koshi, whose high school life
seems to be going so well,
has a secret she can't tell anyone.
She's actually... a former delinquent!
I am the famed wild
beast of Tokyo Hino!
My dark past of being a delinquent
influenced by too much shonen manga!
If this ever comes to light,
all the effort I put into being
an honor student after I quit the gang life
when I got into high school
will go down the drain!
Not that anyone could ever see
through my perfect disguise, though.
That's what she thought…
Up until this very day, that is.
Are you kidding me? We have a suicide by
hanging right in the first episode?!
Should we have gotten
a late-night timeslot?
Not that it would've been much better!
Should I call the police? A doctor?
Detective Co— No, Hajimeeeee!
She's alive? What? If it's not a suicide,
why is she hanging from a place like that?
She has horns?
Ah, that must be those things they
sell at Toky— I mean, Chiba mouseland…
But! Then they'd come off,
and she'd fall, right?!
Which means
those are real horns?!
And most likely deer horns, at that...
There's no world where that's a deer, right?
Also! I mean, only male deer
have horns anyway, right?
Is it some kind of new UMA, then?
Or a mutant
belonging to an evil organization?!
By the way,
that's an incredible amount of snot…
Temperature: 12°C
That's disgusting!
And a bunch of animals are coming here
thinking she's dead meat!
You want a piece of me?
You wanna piece of me, huh?!
Come on, come!
Why is she trying to pick a fight
in this situation?
Actually, should I help her?
She's glaring at me like crazyyy!
The intensity of her gaze!
If I get caught up in this, I'll be late!
But I'm an honor student,
I absolutely cannot be late!
The best course of action is
to pretend I didn't see her
and hurry to school…
You're going to leave me here…
You're really going to abandon me
in this situation…
N-n-n-n-no, of course not, I'd never…
Actually, you're hanging there
of your own accord, aren't you?
And I'm in a real hurry here.
I don't have time to be playing around…
Tomorrow, the news will say:
"A high schooler from Hino got
caught in the electric wires and died"...
From now on, every morning,
when you pass through this street,
you'll remember my face.
Every single day you'll think back
and regret your choice, thinking:
"I should have helped her down that day"...
Okay, I got it!
I'm alive!
This girl's damn heavy!
Hey, Y— Ahem...
Excuse me, why were you up there?
When I woke up this morning
I was there already. I've no idea why…
Seriously, tell me why!
Thanks so much for helping me,
I couldn't have done it without you,
Miss Delinquent.
No, don't mention it...
Did you say "Miss Delinquent"?!
Huh? Who's a delinquent?!
You, girl.
Wh-wh-what are you on about?!
Me? With this beautiful
and composed womanly appearance?
A delinquent?! That's p-p-p-preposterous!!
Oh, really? Hmm, but I can smell it…
Smell what?!
And my horns react to you.
Wait, what kind of sensor is that?!
If I get mixed up with her,
I'll be in trouble.
I-isn't it just your imagination?
Maybe you're mistaking me for someone else…
Oh, I got to get going!
Try not to get caught up again, okay?
Oof, that was close.
I was so sure my disguise was flawless…
How did she…?
What the hell was with that girl?
Okay, everyone, to your seats!
I have a transfer student
to introduce to you.
A transfer student?
I have a bad feeling about this…
Come on in.
Comiiing!
I knew iiiit!!
Wh-why are you stuck again?
Learn already, will ya?!
You're kidding, right?!
Now, Ms. Shikanoko, introduce yourself.
Nroh! I'm Noko Shikanoko,
but you can call me Nokotan!
Nokotan!
What a funny girl.
She's a deer!
Why is everyone welcoming her normally?
Am I the weird one here?
And you can sit…
Next to Ms. Koshi, since it's free there!
This is a common trope in school anime:
the conveniently-free seat.
That's bad! if she says something weird,
my high school life
will definitely be over!
I have to make the first move here.
G-good morning!
Oh, you're that girl!
So you're a transfer student, huh?
I'm Torako Koshi. If you have
any questions, feel free to ask me!
Thank you!
Huh? It seems like it
might be fine after all.
Well, seems like
I didn't need to worry that much!
You can refer to me however you want.
Really?
I was just overthinking things…
Ok! You got it, Miss Delinquent!
Miss Delinquent! Miss Delinquent!
I hope we can get along well,
Miss Delinquent!
Ms. Koshi is a delinquent?!
Koshi, of all people…?!
We heard that wrong, right?!
Hey! you had no reaction to a deer,
what's with the surprise now?!
A d-d-d-delinquent, me?
What are you talking about?
Could you please not make
false allegations?
My instincts are telling me
you're a delinquent, Miss.
Are you a wild beast?!
You're also a virgin, aren't you?
I mean, my horns are reacting to you.
What kind of system is that?!
So Ms. Koshi's a virgin?
I knew Koshi had to be…!
Really?!
Stay out of this!!!
Wh-wh-what kind of proof
do you have to claim I'm a virgin…?
Huh? Then you're not a virgin?
Well, that's… erm…
Virginity confirmed.
It's Ms. Koshi!
She looks beautiful as always!
Just now it seemed like my disgraceful
past was about to come to light…
I'm doing well…
But I can't let my guard down!
I have to make sure that deer
won't expose me as a former delinquent!
To accomplish that,
I must make my move
before she starts saying anything the next—
Is that a mountain of sweets
on my desk for some reason?
No, wait! that cross-shaped package…
Those are deer crackers!
"Deer crackers".
The stereotypical soul food
of the people from Nara Prefecture.
(There's theories as to why).
Some students on their graduation trips
try to eat them for a laugh but,
much like their taste,
that joke is a bit bland, and usually falls flat.
The only one who would do this is…
It definitely was her!!
Wait, is she drooling?
What is she, a merlion?!
Erm, Shikanoko…?
What's the meaning of this?
Hm? That's repayment.
That's not what your face says!
You saved me this morning,
didn't you, Miss?
That's to say thanks.
No, that was no big deal!
There's no need to thank me…
You don't like deer crackers?
That's not the issue here…
Actually, why do you sound
so full of yourself all of a sudden?
How about I give you a horn,
just this once, then?
Can you take them off?!
Here.
I don't want that!!
You can eat them, by the way.
D-does it taste good?
Not that I'll eat it, anyway.
They have no taste, no smell, and are hard!
So you have to force yourself to eat it?!
Tch, if that's how it is…
Here, but just this time.
I don't want them!
And sure, there's that,
but also isn't your identity
going to fall apart like that?
If you don't have your horns,
you're just a common high school girl!
For the one who saved my life…
I don't even mind
dropping my entire character!!
That's too heavy!
And it's too early to get out of character!
It's still the first episode, you know?
You don't want my crackers…
You don't want my horns…
They stick back…
Ah! Could it be that what you want…
Is me?!
(Me=Venison)
Why are you so tied up with the deer thing?
Okay, I got it, you can eat me!
I'm not gonna eat you!
And who are those people??
I mean,
I don't have anything else I can give you!
Look, as you can see,
I don't have any money.
But you still have deer crackers?
Please, don't make me give you anymore…
Why are you acting
like I'm extorting you or something?
And for crackers, of all things!
Oops, my bad! I let my real feelings slip!
Hey, Nokotan!
Did you know about Koshi already?
You two sure look like you're chummy!
Hey! Wait, Nokotan?
That's my nickname! It's cute, isn't it?
Obnoxious!
You see, I was stuck on a power pole
this morning, and Miss Delinq—
Shikanoko! I just remembered
our teacher wanted to see you!
(Do not run in the school hallway)
Oh my, Koshitan... Why bring me here
so suddenly?
That's bold.
What are you imagining?!
I should be asking you,
what did you imagine, Koshitan?
Wh-what are you… I well…
Koshitan…
You're such a virgin!
Shut up?!
And what's with that
"Koshitan" all this time, huh?
It's a nickname.
We're Nokotan and Koshitan,
isn't that great?
Are we a comedy duo?!
Who said you could nickname me?
Well, I'm stuck with Miss Delinq—
Koshitan is okay.
Seems like it's okay.
I mean, that doesn't really matter anyway.
Now, about my real identity.
Can you promise not to tell anyone,
ever, under any circumstances?
I am an honor student here,
so it'd be bad for me
in many ways if anyone
found out about my real identity.
If you do say anything…
It will not end well for you.
You got that?
You mean…
Your real identity is that you're a virgin?
You're… Not wrong, but I don't mean that!
Damn it…
Where do you get off, teasing me like that…
Listen up,
those horns better be your only joke!
You're right…
These are weird, aren't they?
(Indoor)
E... Erm... No...
I mean, of course a girl with horns
would be really disgusting, right?
It's like "What are you?",
"Are you even a deer, huh?", isn't it?
I'm so sorry
if I made you uncomfortable.
I see… She's probably heard horrible
things about her appearance,
and I…
Forget about being an honor student,
I'm a complete failure as a human being!
I-I'm sorry!
I don't mind the horns at all!
So? We're a-okay now, aren't we?
Koshitan wanted to ask
how far her horns went,
but she was scared of the answer.
Today was exhausting…
I still have to prepare
for tomorrow's classes when I get home.
What was that noise?
It came from there?
Excuse me! Is anyone there?
I just heard an incredibly
loud noise, is everything oka—
(Deer)
D-Do I call the police? A doctor?
Detective Co— No, Hajimeeeee!
Ah, Koshitan!
S-Shikanoko, is that b-b-blood?
Did something happen?
Oh, it was my bad!
I fell from the ladder,
and ended up scraping my knee!
And your head? Look at your head!
What a cute band-aid!
Shut up! And what are you doing
in this warehouse no one uses?
I was cleaning!
Cleaning? All by yourself?
Yep! Thanks, Koshitan!
Alright, back to work!
Jeez. I'll help you!
What? Really?!
W-Well, you're hurt,
and who knows
what you'll do if I leave you alone?
Yay! Thanks!
She's an unmistakable Tsundere.
Cleaning is such a chore,
but you seem to be having fun, huh?
I mean, I'm doing it with you, Koshitan!
Y-You're exaggerating!
We're just cleaning!
Even cleaning can be this much fun
when you do it with someone!
Oh, my! It looks so much cleaner already!
Mrs. Ukai?
Nroh, Mrs. Ukai!
Hey there, nroh!
So you helped her out, Ms. Koshi?
Thank you! It must've been hard.
Oh, not at all!
It was pretty easy!
I feel much more at ease knowing you'll be
joining the Deer Club too, Ms. Koshi!
Of cour— Huh? Deer Club?
Well, then, like I promised,
you can use this place however you like.
Yaaay!
Wait, what in the world is a Deer Club?!
And why am I joining?!
What? You didn't hear about it?
I founded the Deer Club here!
What the hell kinda club is that anyway?
I promised her that if she cleaned up
the place she could use it as a clubroom.
-Riiiiight?
"Riiiiight" My left buttcheek!
And ugh, It'll be seriously bad for me
if I get sucked into that senseless club!
I'm so relieved,
Ms. Koshi! You've got it together,
and you're very caring, after all.
Like an older sister!
Since you're so cheerful and kind,
this looks like it'll be a fun club!
It'll be like home for us!
You're also very smart, so you two might
as well get some sort of prize!
We might even get to nationals!
If you're joining, I'm sure
the Deer Club will do incredible things!
Leave it all to me!
Koshitan was easy to get.
Okay, Ms. Shikanoko, make sure
you fill in the club approval form.
Club name: Deer Club.
Club president: Torako Koshi.
Activities: Mainly taking care of deer.
Wait a minute!
Why am I the club president here?
- You're the president, Koshitan.
- You're the president, Ms. Koshi.
Like I said, why me? That's weird!
Isn't this the Deer Club?
If Shikanoko, a literal deer girl, won't be
the president, then who else would?!
That's what you mean?!
But look, here it says the deer club
"mainly takes care of deer", right?
Huh? Yeah…
I'll be the Deer Club's
resident deer, you see…
What's a resident deer?
And the president cares for her!
That's you, Koshitan!
I'm not on board with that!
What kind of club takes care of deer, anyway?
Is this an agricultural school?!
Here, submitted.
And it's definitely accepted.
You work too fast!
Well, then, president, I'm counting on you
to look after Ms. Shikanoko.
I'll be in your care!
Okay.
Since she said "leave it to me"
with such a great smile,
Koshitan couldn't take it back now.
The Deer Club is ready! Hooray!
Things got way too out of hand,
for just one day…
I'll bring more deer crackers tomorrow!
It's okay, I guess.
Well then, should we begin
with a good brushing?
You've gotta be kidding!
And what's with that
scrubber-like brush?
It's for animal use.
Okay, I have no choice then!
Nroh!
Dammit, why do I have to do this…?
Jeez, you're going to make me do
this every club meeting, aren't you?
Damn you, you pest!
S-so scary!
I don't know what's going on,
but it seems
the Deer Club's fight is just beginning!